{
    "1": {
      "question": "The code in The Matrix comes from what food recipes?\n(a) Sushi recipes\n(b) Dumpling recipes\n(c) Stir fry recipes\n(d) Pad thai recipes\n",
      "answer": "a",
      "more_info": "A production designer scanned symbols from his wife's sushi cookbooks, then manipulated them to create the iconic 'code.'",
      "user_response": "None"
    },
    "2": {
      "question": "Who actually drew the sketch of Rose in Titanic?\n(a) Leonardo DiCaprio\n(b) Billy Zane\n(c) James Cameron\n(d) Kathy Bates\n",
      "answer": "c",
      "more_info": "Unlike Jack's French girls, Kate Winslet wore a bathing suit while Cameron sketched the picture.",
      "user_response": "None"
    },
    "3": {
      "question": "What object was Toy Story's Woody originally?\n(a) A ventriloquist dummy\n(b) A puppet\n(c) A clown doll\n(d) A nesting doll\n",
      "answer": "a",
      "more_info": "Even in later versions, Woody was written as a 'sarcastic bully' trying to rally the other toys against Buzz. Luckily, the studio decided to transform him into a more lovable character.",
      "user_response": "None"
    },
     "4": {
      "question": "Which professional athlete was considered for the lead in The Terminator?\n(a) Dan Marino\n(b) Mike Tyson\n(c) O.J. Simpson\n(d) Wayne Gretzky\n",
      "answer": "c",
      "more_info": "Director James Cameron rejected the choice because he didn't think the 'this likable, goofy, kind of innocent guy' could pull off a cyborg assassin.",
      "user_response": "None"
    },
    "5": {
      "question": "How old was the voice actress of Monster Inc.’s Boo at the time of production?\n(a) Four\n(b) Two and a half\n(c) Six\n(d) Ten\n",
      "answer": "b",
      "more_info": "At two and a half, Mary Gibbs had trouble sitting still through the scenes, so the crew would follow her around with a microphone. They'd tickle her or take candy away to make her laugh or cry, so the emotions are as real as they sound.",
      "user_response": "None"
    },
    "6": {
      "question": "Who took home an Oscar for Best Actor in 1998?\n(a) Matt Damon\n(b) Jack Nicholson\n(c) Liam Neeson\n(d) Sean Penn\n",
      "answer": "b",
      "more_info": "Nicholson won the award for his performance in As Good as It Gets.",
      "user_response": "None"
    },
    "7": {
      "question": "Which Star Wars characters appear in Indiana Jones?\n(a) R2D2 and C3PO\n(b) Luke Skywalker and Princess Leia\n(c) Yoda and ObiWan Kenobi\n(d) Han Solo and Chewbacca\n",
      "answer": "a",
      "more_info": "Look closely at the scenery in Raiders of the Lost Ark and you’ll notice hieroglyphics with the robots' likeness in two scenes.",
      "user_response": "None"
    },
    "8": {
      "question": "A Harry Potter stunt double was paralyzed on the job. Which actor did the stunt double do stunts for?\n(a) Rupert Grint\n(b) Emma Watson\n(c) Alan Rickman\n(d) Daniel Radcliffe\n",
      "answer": "d",
      "more_info": "David Holmes did the stunt doubles for Daniel Radcliffe in every Harry Potter movie, but an accident during a flying broomstick scene in the last movie left him paralyzed from the neck down. Radcliffe organized a celebrity charity auction to pay for his medical bills, and Holmes now runs a production company with two other quadriplegic friends.",
      "user_response": "None"
    },
    "9": {
      "question": "Which was the first movie to show a toilet flushing?\n(a) Psycho\n(b) Citizen Kane\n(c) The Graduate \n(d) Vertigo\n",
      "answer": "a",
      "more_info": "At the time, the Motion Picture Production Code banned flushing toilets because it was considered filthy. Psycho was a key to putting the censoring code to an end.",
      "user_response": "None"
    },
    "10": {
      "question": "Dracula was filmed in English during the day, and in what other language at night?\n(a) German\n(b) Swedish\n(c) French\n(d) Spanish\n",
      "answer": "d",
      "more_info": "When the 1931 movie Dracula was being shot, it was common for foreign language films to take over the set at night and shoot their own versions instead of dubbing over them later. The Spanish language version which used the same script and set wrapped up in about half the time and earned way better reviews than its English language counterpart.",
      "user_response": "None"
    }
  }